[Music] Little Fox.
Peter and Benjamin Have a Feast, Episode One: Gathering...
[Music]
...Nuts. Peter and Benjamin were planning a harvest feast.
"We need berries," Peter said.
"Let's gather some nuts too," Benjamin said.
"A harvest feast must have nuts."
The bunnies gathered some berries.
Then they looked for nuts.
Peter and Benjamin saw lots of squirrels.
The squirrels were gathering nuts for winter.
It was hard work.
Peter and Benjamin put their nuts in a pile.
"We have a big pile now," Peter said.
"Hey!" shouted a squirrel. It was Timmy Tiptoes.
Timmy ran toward the bunnies. He pointed at their big pile.
"Are you stealing my nuts?" he asked.
Timmy looked at Benjamin and Peter.
"No," Peter said. "We collected these nuts."
"Hmph," Timmy looked mad. "I put my nuts right there."
"Well, these are our nuts," Benjamin said.
Timmy frowned. "Then where are my nuts?"
Benjamin shrugged. "I don't know."
"But we will find out," Peter said.
Peter and Benjamin Have a Feast, Episode Two: The Nut Thief.
Peter and Benjamin looked for the missing nuts.
Timmy gathered new ones.
"The squirrels are very busy," Peter said. "They are gathering lots of nuts."
"Winter is coming," Benjamin said. "They need—"
"Hey!" a squirrel suddenly shouted. "Look at my pile!"
A second squirrel cried, "Who stole my nuts?" A third squirrel yelled.
More squirrels came running.
One squirrel shouted at Timmy Tiptoes. "Did you steal our nuts?" she cried.
"No," Timmy said. "Someone took some of my nuts too."
"There is a nut thief!" the squirrels shouted back and forth.
Just then, Peter spotted a fat squirrel. "Look, Benjamin," Peter whispered. "It's Silvertail."
Silvertail slipped over to the nut piles.
The squirrels were still fighting. They did not see Silvertail. He took nuts from a pile.
Silvertail hid the nuts under a log.
Then he laughed. "I have lots of nuts for winter. I don't have to work at all!"
Peter and Benjamin Have a Feast, Episode Three: Silvertail.
Peter looked at Benjamin. "Silvertail is the nut thief."
The bunnies ran to the squirrels. "We found the nut thief," Peter said.
"Go away," a squirrel said. "This is not bunny business."
Another yelled, "It is squirrel business."
Timmy looked at the bunnies. "Who is the nut thief?" he asked.
"Come with us," Benjamin said. "We will show you." Timmy followed the bunnies.
They showed him Silvertail's hiding spot. Timmy's eyes got big.
"Wow," he said. "Silvertail is stealing our nuts. We must stop him."
Benjamin saw a hollow tree. It had a hole in its trunk. "Hmm," Benjamin said. "I have an idea."
The bunnies got some nuts.
They hopped to the hollow tree. Then they pushed the nuts into the hole.
"Now let's find Silvertail," Benjamin said.
Silvertail was taking a nap. "Hi, Silvertail!" Peter woke him up.
"We found lots of nuts. Would you like some?"
"Yes," Silvertail licked his lips. "Where are they?"
Peter and Benjamin Have a Feast, Episode 4: The Harvest Feast.
The bunnies brought Silvertail to the tree.
Silvertail looked in the hole. "I don't see any nuts."
Silvertail bent deeper. "Where are—" "Yikes!" Silvertail fell into the hole.
"Help!" he cried. "Oh, I'm stuck!" The bunnies laughed.
"The nut thief is trapped," Peter said. "Goodbye, Silvertail," Benjamin said.
The bunnies told the squirrels about Silvertail. The squirrels stopped fighting.
"I have a great idea," Timmy said. "Let's share our nuts."
The squirrels shared all the nuts. Timmy gave some to the bunnies.
"Thank you for helping us," Timmy said. "We can save these nuts for our feast," Peter said.
At last, it was time for the harvest feast. All the squirrels came.
Timmy rubbed his belly. "These nut pies are delicious!"
Then someone else appeared. Peter gasped. "Silvertail!"
Benjamin laughed. "He's not fat anymore." Silvertail frowned at the bunnies.
"You trapped me in the tree! And where... where are all my nuts?"
Peter pointed to the nut pies. "Right there." Everyone but Silvertail laughed.