Little Fox.
The sun was up.
The sky was blue.
Cat said, "I can jump.
I can jump over the gate.
Watch me jump."
Bat said,
"I can fly. I can fly over the tree.
Watch me fly."
Cow said, "I can walk. I can walk around
the well.
And
I can make a wish."
"A wish," said Bat.
"I want to make a wish."
"So do I," said Cat.
Cow said, "You can make a wish. I will
help you."
Cat and Bat went to the well.
"How do we make a wish?"
said Cat.
"Watch me," said Cow.
"I will show you what to do."
"Tell us, Cow,"
said Cat. "Tell us how to make a wish."
Cow said, "Walk around the well three
times.
Say, 'Please, please, pretty please.'"
Cow went around the well.
She said,
"Please, please, pretty please."
Then Cat went around the well.
She said,
"Please, please, pretty please."
"Two."
Then Bat went around the well.
He said, "Please, please, pretty
please."
Cow said, "Now sing to the well. You
must sing your wish."
Cat sang, "I'm tired of this farm.
I think it is a bore. I want to see new
places
I've never seen before."
"I can't sing," said Bat.
"I will not get my wish."
Cow said, "Just try, Bat." But Bat was too
sad.
"It will not work,"
he said.
"I must fly away now."
Bat flew away.
He did not know how to sing.
He heard Redbird sing.
He tried to sing like Redbird,
but he was not good at all.
He tried to sing like Cat,
Bat sang and sang.
He tried and tried.
He wanted to sing his wish again.
Cat was still at the well,
but she sang a new song.
"Forget the wish I made before.
This is one that I want more.
Please help Bat."
And Bat did sing.
Bat sang to the well,
"Give Cat new things to see."
Then Cat and Bat and Cow went away. They
saw many new things
and they sang.
Pig and Dog were playing catch.
"Good throw, Pig,"
said Dog.
"Good catch, Dog,"
said Pig.
"We are a good team."
Cat woke up.
She saw Pig and Dog playing.
"Can I play catch too?"
asked Cat.
"Okay,"
said Pig.
said Dog.
Cat threw the ball to Pig.
"Too high!" called Pig.
Cat threw the ball to Dog.
"Too low,"
called Dog.
Dog threw the ball to Cat.
Cat missed it.
Pig threw the ball to Cat.
Cat missed it again.
Cat could not throw.
Cat could not catch.
But she liked chasing the ball.
Soon the game was over.
"Catch is fun." Cat said, "Can I play
again?"
"Maybe,"
said Pig.
"We'll see,"
said Dog.
Dog and Pig were playing catch again.
"Can I play?"
asked Cat.
Dog looked at Pig.
Pig looked at Dog.
"No, Cat,"
said Dog.
said Pig.
"Why not?" asked Cat.
"You are not good at catch,"
said Dog.
"You stink,"
said Pig.
"Oh,"
said Cat.
Cat found Bat.
"Pig and Dog are mean,"
she said.
"They said I stink at catch."
"That is mean," said Bat.
"But they are right, Cat. You are not good
at catch."
"Oh,"
said Cat.
She found Cow.
"Bat and Pig and Dog are mean," said Cat.
"They said I stink at catch."
"They're right, Cat," said Cow.
"You are not good at catch."
"Oh,"
said Cat.
Cat ran into the barn.
"I have no friends here.
I will run away."
Cat wrote a note.
"No one loves me.
I am running away."
Then Cat left the barn.
The friends saw the note.
"Cat ran away," Cow cried.
"We did not let Cat play,"
said Dog.
"We said mean things to Cat,"
said Bat.
"I miss Cat,"
said Pig.
"Cat is not good at catch,"
said Dog.
"But she is good at other things."
"Cat is good at running," said Bat.
"Cat is good at sleeping," said Cow.
"Cat is good at sharing,"
said Pig.
"Yes,"
said Dog.
"And she is good at—"
Boom!
The barn door opened.
In came Cat.
"I am good at being friends,"
she said.
"Welcome back, Cat!"
"I missed everyone," said Cat.
"So I came back."
"We are a good team," said Pig.
```