Little Fox.
Bat saw something brown.
He went to tell Cow.
I saw something brown. Said Bat.
Is it a hat? Said Cow.
It is not a hat. Said Bat.
He went to Pig.
I saw something brown and hard. Said
Bat.
It's not a hat.
Is it a box? Said Pig. A box is brown
and hard.
It is not a box. Said Bat.
Bat went to Cat.
I saw something in the barn. Said Bat.
It is brown and hard and small.
It is not a hat or a box.
Is it a rock? Said Cat.
A rock is brown and hard.
A rock can be small, too. Cat said.
It is not a rock. Said Bat.
Bat went back to the barn.
What was this thing?
Come look at this thing. Said Bat.
It is not a hat.
It is not a box.
It is not a rock. Said Bat.
It is brown.
It is hard.
And it is small. Said Bat.
Can you tell me what it is?
They all went into the barn.
The thing is over there. Said Bat.
They went to the spot.
They looked at the thing.
You said the thing is brown. Said Cow.
This thing is not brown.
You said the thing is hard.
This thing is not hard. Said Pig.
You said the thing is small. Said Cat.
You are right.
This thing is very small.
Bat flew over.
He looked at the thing again.
But where is the thing I saw? Said Bat.
I do not see it now.
Bat looked and looked.
The thing that was brown and hard was
not there.
This thing was yellow.
This thing was soft.
The thing made a sound.
It said
Cat said Bat what is this thing?
It is a chick. Said Bat.
It is a soft yellow chick.
I found it. Said Bat.
So it is mine.
Right?
No. Said Cow.
The chick must go to its mother.
But you have something, too. Said Cow.
What do I have? Said Bat.
You have a story. Said Cow.
It is about the thing in the barn.
You can tell this story to your friends.
And that is what Bat did.
Bat flew over the barn.
He saw a fox.
Bat flew into the barn.
A fox is coming. He said.
Cat woke up.
A fox is coming? She asked.
Pig ran into the barn.
A fox is coming? He asked.
Yes. Said Bat.
A fox is coming to our farm.
Oh, no. Said Cat.
We must do something.
The fox will see the hen house. Said
Pig.
It will eat the hens.
Let's get dog. Said Cat.
He will scare the fox away.
No. Said Cow.
Dog is sick today.
We must let him sleep.
We can stop the fox. Said Bat.
I know what to do.
Pig looked at Bat.
Cat looked at Bat.
Cow looked at Bat.
The fox is coming. Said Pig.
We have to do something. Said Cat.
We can hide. Said Bat.
Cow, you hide behind the hen house.
Pig, you hide behind the tractor.
Cat, you hide behind the windmill.
Where will you go? Cow asked Bat.
I will go to an apple tree. Said Bat.
Soon, the fox will be here. Said Bat.
And we will make some noise.
So Cow went to the hen house.
Pig went to the tractor.
Cat went to the windmill.
Bat flew to an apple tree.
They all waited.
They waited for the fox to come.
Bat watched from the apple tree.
Cow watched from the hen house.
Pig watched from the tractor.
Cat watched from the windmill.
At last, the fox came.
It looked all around.
Then it went to the hen house.
"Now!" cried Bat.
Bat swooped down at the fox.
Cat hissed at the fox.
Pig oinked at the fox.
Cow mooed at the fox.
Then they all did it again.
Swoop!
Hiss!
Oink!
Moo!
The fox ran fast.
The fox ran far.
"We did it!" cried Pig.
The noise was loud.
It woke up dog.
"You were sleeping." said Cat.
"So?"
"We watched the farm." said Pig.
"Thank you." said Dog.
He felt much better now.